<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Sportsdevos]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Sportsdevos]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 05:21:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hail Mary]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Hail Mary</h1><p>When the distance to the goal line is long and time
is short, football coaches call a Hail Mary pass.
The quarterback is not able to target particular receiv-
ers; he just throws deep down</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/hail-mary/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">27682f2f-dd6a-4a9c-b69a-490cca6d60e6</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 05:21:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Counter Play]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Counter Play</h1><p>The counter play in football is simple; the entire
offense heads in one direction while the running
back cuts and heads the opposite way. Do you know
that Christianity is really a counter play? The world
advises, “Do it on your own.” Christ says, “I’ll do it for
you.” The world suggests, “Advance by domination.”
Christ says, “Advance by service.” The world chants,
“Seize it now.” Christ says “Wait for the kingdom to
come.” The world cries, “Vengeance!” Christ whispers, “Forgiveness!”
The world says, “All roads lead to heaven.” Christ
says, “I am the way, and the truth, and the life!” The
world calls standard plays, resulting in brokenness and
separation. But you can “run the counter” by trusting
in Christ, instead of yourself, and this world.
“The world and its desires pass away, but whoever does
the will of God lives forever” (I John 2:17). </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/the-counter-play/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">73b1ca75-a3de-466f-b854-124ef8c760f3</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 05:19:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Forgiveness Business]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Forgiveness Business</h1><p>God is involved in many different industries; creation, life, and judgment for sure. But there is one
enterprise that we see him engaged in throughout The
</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/the-forgiveness-business/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a930929b-7b51-426f-9321-8fbb2aead7f9</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 05:16:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Never Too Late]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Never Too Late</h1><p>Here is one of the most hopeful phrases in the English language, “It’s Never Too Late!” Have you
heard that deceptive voice bellowing, “It’s too late,
you’ve missed your chance!” That is a lie. You can
have another chance. The most hopeful book in the
world - The Bible is filled with people who looked like
they were out of time, out of resources, out of hope. But
when they called on the name of the Lord, with repen-
tance and humility, everything changed! Their situa-
tion, their circumstance, and their life course became
dramatically different. God can do the same for you.
It’s Never Too Late!
 </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/never-too-late/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3c244e22-40dc-4dcf-ad46-c2e51bba358c</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 05:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triple Play]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Triple Play</h1><p>Triple plays are rare jewels to witness. One night,
a guy playing shortstop called out to his girlfriend
playing second before the pitch and said, “Hey babe
</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/triple-play/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">fa5f88b1-2ca7-43d5-9d9a-dc39eb168ef6</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 05:12:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>People often didn’t realize the degree of skill and

athleticism necessary to play in a competitive sport 

league. Let’s be honest, if a player doesn’t have at 

least above average proficiency then they may not be 

ready to play at the top level. Did you know that there 

are eligibility requirements to be on God’s team? Oh 

yes that’s right. Not heritage, resources, appearance or 

performance. Making the squad requires comprehensive 

repentance. No qualification, just a proper response to 

His majesty. Only one thing determines who makes the 

heavenly roster - a sorrowful turn of the heart towards 

Christ’s gift of eternal life.

“For Godly grief produces a repentance that leads to 

salvation without regret, whereas worldly grief produces death” (2 Cor 7:10). </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/d83f28d0-5fcc-450c-941b-29099aec32e4/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d83f28d0-5fcc-450c-941b-29099aec32e4</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 06:12:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safe With The Savior Sports Devotional]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Safe With The Savior Sports Devotional</h1><p>Baseball & softball feature lots of sprinting. From

the moment the ball pings off the bat, players 

begin racing around. We run toward security, we scurry 

to avoid the tag. All we want is to be safe, on that base, 

freed from the penalties of our sin and the weariness of 

life’s trials. While you’re running, you’re in danger, 

unsafe until you make contact with the Savior. That’s 

where true security is found. And when you land on 

His base, no matter what, He chases after you and will 

bring you all the way home!

“There is therefore now no condemnation for those 

who are in Christ Jesus” (Rom 8:1).</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/safe-with-the-savior-sports-devotional/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">28771772-49dc-4462-9cb6-54b65ec47c16</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 03:19:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Freedom Sports Devotion]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Freedom Sports Devotion</h1><p>Every week on the news we find another group of

people wrestling for their liberty from powerful 

forces that seek to restrain them. In every corner of 

globe this struggle rages. The thirst for freedom is universal as our hearts instinctively yearn to come out from 

under the rule of dictators. Jesus Christ is the greatest 

Freedom Fighter. The bible says that, “It is for freedom that Christ set us free...” (Gal 5:1). He sets us free 

spiritually from the debilitating darkness of sin, and 

unshackles us from anything that holds us back... debt / 

fear/ wounds/ insecurity/ addictions/ laziness. There is 

nothing that Christ the liberator cannot conquer.

“Where the spirit of the Lord is, there is Freedom” 

(2 Cor 3:17). </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/5eff7dfe7415c4893d0e45d921773c61db3c321b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/freedom-sports-devotion/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4f255fd3-ace3-446d-901a-ac961e53798c</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 03:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>