<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Sportsdevos]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Sportsdevos]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 16:50:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rules Of The Game]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Rules Of The Game</h1><p>Every game has rules that define the boundaries of

appropriate play and ensure equitable competition. 

Without rules there would be no order, and the game 

would descend into crisis. Do you recognize the moral 

law, God’s transcendent standards for human behavior? 

The first commandment directs our attention upward 

to our Heavenly Father. We are to give thanks to Him 

as our life giver and sustainer. He is the source of all 

creation and we are commanded to recognize this truth 

and worship Him accordingly. It is His rules that should 

guide our entire life, still we obstinately rebel. Thank-
fully God the Father gave us the law, and Jesus Christ 

lived it out by righteously offering Himself up in order 

to earn our amnesty.

“He made Him who knew no sin to be sin on our behalf, 

so that we might become the righteousness of God in 

Him” (2 Cor 5:21). </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/rules-of-the-game/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">66f0165a-44a0-4917-bf18-43bd4e087103</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 16:50:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Average]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Average</h1><p>As a fundraiser, a high school had a men’s volleyball team that was coached by the female volley-
ball players. All the baseball, football, and basketball 

players trotted out to try their hand at the new sport. 

They were not volleyball players, so skills were average, but effort was high. One guy played outside hitter 

and his technique was to hit the ball with a closed fist. 

This form allowed a strong strike but little control to 

keep the ball in bounds. But when one of the coaches 

showed them how to hit with an open hand, everything 

changed. His spikes had more power and his ball control improved dramatically. They were completely 

transformed volleyball players. All of us naturally live 

closed fisted lives towards God, but when we loosen 

our grip toward him, we finally breakthrough! When 

we open up to the Living God we find restoration, we 

“...I will confess my transgressions to the Lord and 

you forgave the iniquity of my sin” (Ps 32:5). </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/average/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">32527565-b395-42f0-a331-0077b7c985c6</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 16:48:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Making The Team]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Making The Team</h1><p>In the great sport movie, Rudy, we see a man who
badly desires to be a part of a certain team. He is
willing to do literally anything to play football for
Notre Dame; leaving everything he knows behind,
sleeping in a shed, and suffering physical beating on
the practice team. He’s fueled by the dream of running
out onto that field wearing a golden helmet.
  </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/making-the-team/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">498fea26-4412-4832-a1c3-8df5e756bc42</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 05:56:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pump Fake]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Pump Fake</h1><p>With the ball in hand, the quarterback drops back
and goes through the throwing motion. But he
doesn’t release the ball and instead pitches to a differ-
ent teammate. Many people pump fake on God, going
through the motions of a phony routine. A nice suit and
a ritual coupled with a life of willful rebellion. They
state noble intentions, but hold on to their sin, side-
stepping the fullness of life available through genuine
relationship with Christ Jesus. With a pump fake nothing happens. No action occurs, it’s a vain move. An
actual throw produces motion; it puts the ball into play
for a connection with Christ and brings life to the full
and life eternal. Pump fakes will never spiritually suffice, but a genuine outpouring of repentance will result
in relationship.

</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/pump-fake/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8f10a0dd-322d-40fd-abdb-d2cf4a63eb75</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 05:54:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Audible]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Audible</h1><p>A play has been called, the offense runs up to the
line of scrimmage. But as the quarterback surveys
the defense he doesn’t like what he sees; running the
same play may bring unfavorable results. Therefore he
calls an audible. Our lives before Christ are made up of
the same schemes, and predictable offenses; deceiving,
carousing, and cheating. It’s time for us to call an audi-
ble. A Christ follower has actually </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/audible/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0e3e1fac-a293-48c9-8570-ecd2c7e99f92</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 05:39:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Button Hook]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Button Hook</h1><p>One of the worst plays a football receiver learns is
the button hook. The mechanics are simple;
the receiver runs full speed and the QB launches the ball while you are running. Then you turn completely
around to catch the airborne ball before the defensive
player can react. We’ve all run full speed into trouble,
streaking away from God. We’ve employed our own
game plan, at our pace, based upon our own rules. But
in His grace, He has thrown the plan of salvation our
way. While we were sprinting out of bounds, Christ
walked to the cross. While we lived in unrighteous-
ness, He lived a perfect life. The only response needed
is to turn completely to receive His new life. A Christian simply defined is one who has run the button hook.
He ran away with the world, but turned to catch the
Gospel!
“While we were yet sinners Christ died for us” (Rom 5:8)
. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/button-hook/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c68ada93-8497-4e2e-a291-315b1d43d76f</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 05:33:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Blocker]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Blocker</h1><p>The set is up, the hitter is in the air... spike! But
no it’s blocked! </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/the-blocker/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e2c7cbf6-a13e-4a31-a7f2-bbfa2ed57631</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 05:30:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quarterback Sneak]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Quarterback Sneak</h1><p>One of the most commonly run plays in all levels
of football is the quarterback keeper. The one
expected to throw becomes the rusher. The one pro-
</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/quarterback-sneak/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d94275a4-3a90-4c2e-acdb-18d7f94f0171</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 05:28:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Round The Bases]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Round The Bases</h1><p>Goal of baseball - Get your teammates all the way
around the bases and back home.
</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/round-the-bases/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cf163d21-6164-4330-8cf7-5a67ef5cb207</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 05:24:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hail Mary]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Hail Mary</h1><p>When the distance to the goal line is long and time
is short, football coaches call a Hail Mary pass.
The quarterback is not able to target particular receiv-
ers; he just throws deep down</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sportsdevos/hail-mary/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">27682f2f-dd6a-4a9c-b69a-490cca6d60e6</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 05:21:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>